{
    "subject": "resource/XChange_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Allan_Moyle",
    "human_readable": "Allan Moyle directed the film XChange.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8540064096450806,
            "question": "Who directed the film XChange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8407880663871765,
            "question": "Is Allan Moyle known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7969903349876404,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Allan Moyle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7687941193580627,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Allan Moyle."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6905366778373718,
            "question": "Who starred in the film XChange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5123031735420227,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Allan Moyle that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4781247079372406,
            "question": "When was the film XChange released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3637610673904419,
            "question": "What genre is the film XChange likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30831459164619446,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of XChange?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20078648626804352,
            "question": "What awards or recognition did XChange receive?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Allan Moyle directed the film XChange.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3512_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of XChange?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3512_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film XChange likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3512_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film XChange released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3512_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3512_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Allan Moyle directed the films \"Xchange 2001\" and other films, thus supporting the statement that Allan Moyle directed the film \"XChange\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}